Ben Wisialowski

Currently spending one year traveling and taking time to explore my interests in generative art, IoT, scuba diving, and environmental health. I am intending on re-entering the workforce in Summer 2019.

+1 (650) 773-9116 ben@wiz3.com linkedin.com/in/benwiz github.com/benwiz www.benwiz.io

EXPERIENCE

Lucid, New Orleans — Senior Engineer, Platform Integrations

DECEMBER 2016 - MARCH 2018 (Engineer), MARCH 2018 - JULY 2018 (Senior Engineer)
Supported internal and external stakeholders throughout the entire integration process from sales to development though continued support.

Worked closely with colleagues in all departments to identify then improve operations. Usually this was through web-based automation using Django, Airflow, Python, and AWS Lambda FaaS. I deployed one project in Go.

Encouraged discussion and excitement for innovation within Lucid.

${\bf Grok+Banter,\ New\ Orleans-\it Developer+Information\ Analyst}$

JANUARY 2016 - OCTOBER 2016

Experimented, designed, and implemented a solution to measure the effectiveness of out-of-home advertisements using OpenCV and DLib computer vision frameworks deployed to various system-on-a-chip hardware products.

Identified and introduced potential clients to our product at conferences.

BragOn, LLC, New Orleans — Founder, iOS Developer

MARCH 2014 - MAY 2015

Founded LLC and published mobile shopping iPhone app to connect consumers with local retailers.

EDUCATION

Tulane University, New Orleans — B.S. in Economics & C.S.

AUGUST 2011 - MAY 2015

PROJECTS

WWOZ-to-Spotify, AWS Lambda — *Clojure*

github.com/benwiz/wwoz_to_spotify

Scrape radio station WWOZ's RSS feed and import songs into a Spotify playlist in real time. Improved github.com/blmstm/clj-spotify auth workflow.

SKILLS

Bridging the gap between tech and non-tech by patiently listening and teaching.

Learning quickly with an attention to best practices.

Rapidly designing and implementing prototypes.

Elegant design in software architecture and visuals.

TOOLS and LANGUAGES

Advanced: Python, JavaScript, bash, Django, Hapi.js, Docker, AWS (Lambda, S3, RDS, ElasticBeanstalk, Route 53)

Mediocre: Go, Airflow, Kafka, Redis, Flask, OpenCV, AWS (ElastiCache, ElasticSearch)

Beginner: Clojure, C++, openFrameworks

INTERESTS and FUN FACTS

Generative art, audiobooks, brain-computer interfaces, environmental health, IoT

Visited 33 countries, karate black belt, jiu-jitsu white belt, soon-to-be scuba divemaster